Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Audio
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    - Voidoids -late show- July 2, 1978 CBGB *Feelies July 2nd II/ Feelies Hurrah July 19, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0090)
      Side A: Third Uncle, I'm Free, Beware, Walkin, Kid, Amuse
      Side B: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Night, Work, Loveless Love
    - The Feelies/ MUDD Dec 29, 1978 CBGB Happy Spring Cont'd, December 29, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0091)
      Side A: Boy, Original Love, Work, [Track Unknown], Fa Ce La, [Track Unknown], Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythms, Lookin At You, Third Uncle
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, [Track Unknown], Fa Ce La, Loveless Love, Raised Eyebrows, Crazy Rhythm, Lookin At You
    - Cramps Pep lounge Feb 25-26 '83 "Smell of Female", 1983 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0092)
    - Commander Cody & His Lost Planet Airmen, Live at the Academy, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0093)
      Side A: Wine Do Your Stuff, Truck Drivin' Man, Seeds 'n' Stems, Lookin' at the World thru a Windshield, Sunset on the Sage, Boogie Man, Daddy's Drinkin up Our Christmas, Diggy Liggy Lo, Sea Cruise, That's What I Like about the South, Ernie's Thing, Andy's Thing
      Side B: Milk Cow Blues, Four/Five Times, I'm Comin' Home, Mama Tried, House of Delights, Oh Mama Mama, Cryin' Time, I Saw the Light, Beat Me Daddy, Hot Rod Lincoln
    - Commander Cody & His Lost Planet Airmen Live/ Johnny M, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0094)
      Side A: Root in Cell #9, Too Much Fun, Don't Let Go, Jailhouse Rock, Mean Woman Blues, Lost in the Ozone, Hey Hey Hey
      Side B: Mahavishnu Orch[estra] Live [wooward race], Miles Davis Sivad
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra Dec 28, 1973, Philharmonic Hall, December 28, 1973 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0095)
      Side A: Dream (cont'd), No Name (Goodman), Love Supreme, Awakening Jam
      Side B. Hope (encore), The Noonward Race
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra Central Park, June 24, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0096)
      Side A: Power of Love
      Side B: (cont'd) - Smile of the Beyond, Hymn to Him
    - Mahavishnu Live at Ithaca College, Oct 26 1974, October 26, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0097)
    - Mahavishnu Live in Central Park, June 24, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0098)
    - David Bowie - July 19, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0099)
      Side A: 1984, Rebel Rebel, Moonage Daydream, Boys-It's a Sweet Thing- Changes- Suffragette City
      Side B: Alladin Sane, All the Young Dudes, Cracked Actor, Rock n Roll with Me, Watch That Man, Knock on Wood, Space Oddity
      Tape Length:90 minutes
    - Roxy Music live in London Oct 17th 1975, Wembley Empire - Poor Copy, October 17, 1975 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0100)
    - Mahavishnu, Oct 26, 1974 Live at Ithaca College, October 26, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0101)
    - Chick Corea Return to Forever / Gato, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0102)
    - Oregon Live at the Unicorn April 6th 1975, April 6, 1975 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0103)
    - Santana Oct 14, 1974/ DR Demento, October 14, 1974 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0104)
    - Santana, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0105)
    - Hell, Glenn O'Brien, Folk City April 25 '84/ Hell, Joey Ramone, [Cramps] April 4, '84 WBAI, 1984 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0106)
      Side A: Richard Hell- Folk City 4-25-84, Glen[n] Obrien- Tramps 4-25-84
      Side B: Richard Hell- WBAI Interview, Joey Ramone Interview
    - Lloyd w/Bidwell New Group Aug 7 '80 CBGB Squat Set 25 '80, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0107)
    - Lloyd's Quartet - Town Hall, March 30 '80. Dead Boys -same-, March 30, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0108)
      Side A: She Said No, I Can Tell, Alchemy, Misty Eyes, Now That She Has Gone
    - Lloyd & Co - [Peprum Lounge] Jan 22, 1981, January 22, 1981 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0109)
    - Bloods VOIDOIDS Feb 27 '81 Pep Lounge, February 27, 1981 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0110)
      Side A: Kid, Ignore That Door
    - Hell, Void-Oids CBGB Thursday the [___] of September 1979, two sets (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0111)
      Side A: Kid, [Track Unknown], Lowest Common Dominator, I'm Gone, __ Spurts, Crack of Dawn, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Game of Love, You Gotta Lose, Ignore That Door
      Side B: (?) Spurts, Dominator, [Track Unknown], Staring in Her Eyes, New Pleasure, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Another World, [Track Unknown], Walkin on the Water, Kid, Liars Beware
    - Hell/ Student teacher's, Hell/ 57 Club, March 30 -79, March 30, 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0112)
      Side A: Staring in Her Eye, You Gotta Lose, ___ Spurts, New Pleasure
      Side B: [Track Unknown], Walkin on the Water, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], ___ Spurts, Who Says?, [Track Unknown], Another World
    - Void-Oids & Patti - Palladium May 20 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0113)
      Side A: ___Spurts, Liars Beware, Kid With the Replac[e]able Head, Walkin' on the Water, Blank, I Wanna Be Your Dog
    - Void-Oids, April 20 1978 CBGB Thursday late show with Erasers/ Hell Solo, Bottom Line Aug 1984, 1978/1984 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0114)
      Sides A and B: Venus, Walking in Rain, I Don't Love Anyone, #7, Liars Beware, Kid with the Replac[e]able Head, New Pleasure, Betra[ya]l Takes Two, Ventilator Blues, Spurts, Blank, Be Your Dog, All theWay
    - VoidOids Hell, Max's - Jan 27 '77 2 sets, Aug 18 '78 one set, 1977/1978 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0115)
      Sides A and B: Spurts, Liars Beware, New Pleasure, The Plan, You Gotta Lose, Walkin on the Water, I'm Your Man, Time Stands Still, Blank/Liars Beware, Walkin on the Water, I'm Your Man, Betrayal Takes Two, New Pleasure, Another World, Spurts, Blank/ Blank.
    - Hell, Punk Benefit May 4-5 '77, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0116)
      Sides A and B: Blank, Walkin on the Water, New Pleasure, Betrayal Takes Two, Rock 'n' Roll Club, Spurts/ Spurts, Liars Beware, Another World, New Pleasure
    - VoidOids, sound check 4/17/77 CBGB/ Patti Smith Group, May 4, 1977 CBGB Punk Benefit with Matthew Reich (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0117)
      Side A: Spurts, I'm Your Man, Ventilator Blues, I Wanna Be Your Dog
      Side B: Kimberly, Pissing in the River, Gimme Some Lovin', Chain Gang, (Boyfriendx), Waiting For My Man
      Format: 1/4" Audiocassette
      Tape Length: 46 minutes
    - Heartbreakers Demos/ VoidOids April 14 '77, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0118)
      Sides A and B (New Pleasure): Spurts, New Pleasure, Liars Beware, The Plan, You Gotta Lose, Another World, 7. Rock n Roll Club, Blank
    - VoidOids, Max's 27 1-27-77, January 27, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0119)
      Sides And B: Set I: Spurts, Liars, New Pleasure, Lose, Walking, I'm Your Man, Blank/ Set II: Liars, Walkin', I'm Your Man, Betrayal
      Container Annotation: Richard Hell Voidoids at Max's 11:40-12:10 am; 1:35-2:10 am 65 minutes
      Recording Length (tape annotation): 65 minutes
    - The Void-Oids Live Nov 19th & 20th / Single Patti Smith at Bottom Line Monday 22nd November w/ Lee Fox Bass, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0120)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Love Comes in Spurts, the Plan, All the Way, Time Stands Still, I'm Your Mom, Blank Generation, [Track Unknown], You Gotta Lose, New Pleasure, The Plan, All the Way, Blank Generation, Love Comes, Another World, You Gotta Lose, Blank Generation
      Side B: Jesse James, Kimberly, Jam/J.A., Ask ME, Angels, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Pumpin'
      R. Hell - Vocal, Bass; Marc Bell - Drums; Ivan Julian - Guitar, Robert Quine - Guitar/Bottom Line Monday 22nd November w/ Lee fox - Bass
    - Shirts - The Heartbreakers Live July 25, 1975 CBGB during RnR Festival summer of '75/Dolls 73/74 Detriot Michigan Place, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0121)
      Sides A and B: Going Steady, Chinese Rocks, [Pirate Cove], Eyes on You, Flight, Nothin Better To Do, Blank, I Wanna Be Loved, New Pleasure, Flo & Eddie on Lou, Human Being, Pills, Trash, Give Her a Great Big Kiss ([Fla] '74), Chatterbox
      The Hearbreakers 7/25 Live at CBGB during R n' R Festival Summer of '75; Dolls 73/74 Detroit Michigan Palace
    - CBGB Aug 13, 1978- Lloyd, Daugherty, Smith, Fliegler, Brody- zak-Lenny, Lisa Burns, Daugherty-r-guitar & Jesse- Drums, Genja Ravan, H. Goldman (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0122)
      Side A: Pretty Vacant, Love Me Do, Heartaches, Monster Mash (with Zak), Whiter Shade of Pale (with Lenny), Crazy Like a Fox, Tumblin' Dice
      Side B: Lola, Fever, Messin w/the kid
      Lisa Burns, Dougherty - r. guitar, Jesse - drums, [Genja Ravam], H. Goldman
    - Lloyd- Max's Friday Jan 12, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0123)
      Sides A and B: Watch Yourself, Won't Give Her Up, She Said No, Woman's Ways, Pretend, [Track Unknown], In the Night, Should Have Known Better
    - Lloyd Quartet CBGB March 4th '79, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0124)
      Side A: Alchemy, Number Nine, Better Watch Yourself, Dying Words, Woman's Ways
    - Lloyd & Co. June 3, 78- Max's Patti [F.] Smith, B. Brady, J.D. Daugherty, R Fleigler, L. Kaye/ Crayola Max's June 4, '78, 1978 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0125)
      Side A (Lloyd): Gimmie Some Lovin', Rebel Rebel, Glad All Over, Back Door Man, Today I Met the Boy..., Under My Thumb, Don't Bring Me Down, Can Ya Hear Me Knockin'
      Side B (Lloyd/Crayola): Miss You
    - Birdland CBGB Jan 3, 1979 2nd Show CBGB/ Lloyd (solo) MUD Jan 5, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0126)
      Side A: Watch Yourself, Won't Let Her Go, Dying Words, Woman's Ways, Looking Through Me
    - Lloyd Quintet Fri June 29 '79 Max's 1st of ?/ Neon Boys '73, 1979/1973 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0127)
      Side A: Misty Eyes
      Currently there is no access to this title. Please contact Fales Library.
    - Lloyd Quintet CBGB Thursday 13 Sept, '79 Part of Early Most of Late, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0128)
      Side A: Blue & Grey, Woman's Ways, Misty Eyes, Just Like Smoke
    - Lloyd Dec 9, '79 CBGB Sunday Late, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0129)
      Side A (Fall): Pretend
      Side B (Lloyd CBGB Dec 9th '79 Sunday Late): Tracks Unknown
    - Lloyd Dec 7, 8, 9th CBGB Friday Late, Sat Late, Sunday Early, 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0130)
      Side A (Lloyd CBGB Friday the 7th Late Show/Lloyd CBGB Saturday the 8th Late Show): [Track Unknown], I Can Tell, She's My Girl, Should Have Known, [Track Unknown], Alchemy, #9, Just Like Smoke, I Can Tell
      Side B (Sat Cont'd, Sunday Early): I Can Tell (cont'd), Summer Rain, Misty Eyes, She's My Girl, Watch Yourself, Get Off My Cloud, I Can Tell, Woman's Ways, Alchemy
    - Lloyd Oct 18th CBGB Thursday Late Show, 1979/ Dec 7, CBGB Friday Early '79 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0131)
      Side A: Watch Yourself, In the Night, Blue & Gray, #9, I Won't Give her Up, Womans' Ways, Just Like Smoke, She's My Girl, Misty Eyes
      Side B: Dying Words, I Can Tell (Cut), Pretend, #9, Alchemy, Watch Yourselves
    - Richard Lloyd, Heat Dec 27, 28 1979 one set each night (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0132)
      Side A (Lloyd- Heat Dec 2 1979/Lloyd Dec 28)
      Side B (Lloyd Cont'd)
    - Lloyd one set March 13 CBGB- snowstorm- Second Set March 15- 1980 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0133)
      Sides A and B: She Said No, I Can Tell, Misty Eyes, Alchemy, Number/Nine, She's My Girl, Yes & No, Watch Yourself, [Track Unknown], She Said No
    - Patti Smith Dec 26 '75 Bottom Line, 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0134)
      Side A: Jessee James, We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Privilage, Ain't it Strange, Space Monkey, Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Pumpin, Birdland, Land
      Side B: Gloria, Time Is On My Side, My Generation
    - [Based on Container Annotation]-- Patti Smith -Bottomline- Radio- Dec 27, 1975/[Based on Cassette Annotation]-- Side A: Roxy Music/ Side B June 1974, 1974/1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0135)
      Content: [On container]
      Sides A and B: Real Good Time Together, [Track Unknown], Strained On Strange, Space Monkey, Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Pumpin', Mafia, Land, Gloria, Time is on My Side, My Generation - Mummers Parade St Marks New Years Eve 1974-75
    - [Based on Container Annotation]--Patti Smith Columbia U April 1975/ [Based on Cassette Annotation]-- A) Kind Crimson's Lark's Tonight/B)Starless Bible Black (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0136)
      Content: [On Container]
      Nigger, Seventh Heaven, Jeanne D'arc, What Make Ruda Ivory, Picasso Laughing, Sunday Evenings Down South, Rape, Rimbaud Dead, Born to be Me, Gilbrato, Christ died, All the Hipsters Have Gone to the Movies, Sonnett, Piss Factory
    - Patti Smith Live WBAI 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0137)
      Content: Lou 4/26/75 cont'd- Oh Jim- White Light/
      Sides A and B: Real Good Time, Hunter, Birdland, Redondo Beach, Space Monkey, Snowball, Distant Fingers, Break it up, Gloria, We Walk Down the Aisle of love
    - Television CBGB (Patti) '75 Rock's Tapes, 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0138)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Prove it, Venus, Friction, Blank, Double Exposure/Fire Engine, Prove it, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jane
      Side B: Friction, Kingdom Come/Real Good Time Together, Redondo Beach, Birdland, Space Monkey, Distant Fingers, Gloria
    - Patti Smith March 22, 1975 CBGB- Late show/ June 29, 1975 The Other End, March 22; June 29, 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0139)
      Side A: Hunter, Magellan, Piss Factory, We Three, Free Money, Break It Up, Land /Real Good Time, Redondo Beach, [Track Unknown]
      Side B: Birdland, Space Monkey, Snowball, Distant Fingers, Break It Up, Gloria, Time is on My Side, Piss Factory (encore)
    - Patti Smith Max's Sept 1, 1974- Patti-Vocal, Lenny Kaye-Guitar, R Shol- Piano/ Reno Sweeney Dec 9, 1973 Patti-Vocal & Piano, Lenny Kaye-Guitar, 1973/1974 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0140)
      Side A (9/1/74): Real Good Time Marco, Polo, I'm Wild about That Thing, Harbour Spill, Hunter, Piss Factory, We Three, Land, Hey Joe, Speak Low, Autobiography, Seventh Heaven
      Side B (12/9/73): I Don't Love Nobody, Mon Vieux Lucien, Just An Accident, Sally, Jesse James, Annie Had A Baby, Ballad of the Bad Boy, 4 Interesting Positions, I Get a Kick Out of You, Piano Sacrifice, Steve McAvoy, Fire of Unknown Origins, Jimbo
    - Patti Smith- March 20, 1975 CBGB- Patti -vocal, Lenny Kaye- guitar, Richard Sohl-Piano, Ivan Kral -guitars (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0141)
      Side A: Real Good Time, Redondo Beach, Sherry, Space Monkey, Birdland, Break It Up, Gloria
      Side B: Hunter, Just Like Magellan, We Three, Free Money, Distant Fingers, Land
    - Patti Smith Live at Reno Sweeney's, Max's, My Father's Place + single, 1973/1974 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0142)
      Side A (Reno Sweeney 29 Dec '73, Max's 1 Sept '74): We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Captured by the Game, Good Time, Gloria (version), Free Money, Break it Up, Horses, Piss Factory (single)
      Side B: Hey Joe (single), [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown],Jesse James, Annie Had A Baby, Ballad of a Baby Boy, I Get a Kick Out of You, Real Good Time
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1, Part 2, and Part 3.
    - Patti Smith -February 15th 1975 CBGB- Patti-vocals, Lenny Kaye-Vocal, guitar, Richard Sohl- Piano Bass, Ivan Kral- Guitar Bass, Tom Verlaine-Piano, February 15, 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0143)
      Side A: Real Good Time Together, Hunter, Birdland, Space Monkey, Break it Up, Gloria
      Side B: Any Day of the Week, Piss Factory, We Three, Free Moneym Harbor Spell, Land
    - Patti Smith Live at Cleveland's Agora, WMMS FM on Jan 26, 1976- Patti-vocals, Lenny-Guitar, DNV-Piano Ivan Kral-Bass Rhythm, Jay Dee Daugherty-Drums, John Cale - Bass (My Generation), January 26, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0144)
      Side A: We're Gonna Have a Real Good Time Together, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Birdland, Break it Up
      Side B: Break it Up (cont'd), Land, Gloria, Time is on My Side
    - Patti Smith Live at the Hammersmith Odeon Featuring Tapper Zukie, Jah Don, October 23, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0145)
      Sides A and B: Redondo Beach, Free Money, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Ask The Angels, Time is on My Side, Pumpin', Aint it Strange, Gloria, Land of 1000 Dances
      Container Annotation: "Yea Pete that’s me talking over radio Ethiopia might sound strange, but it got good reviews"
    - Patti Smith Live at the Roxy 1/30/76, January 30, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0146)
      Side A: Tapper Zukie "Man ah Warrior", P. Smith "Hey Joe/ Pissfactory + assort.
      Side B (Patti Smith Live at Roxy 1/30/76) Realblood Time, Ain't it Strange, Redondo, Pale Blue Eyes, Louie Louie, Birdland, Gloria, Kimberly
    - Patti Smith Group + friends, March 9th 1977, David Johansen, Tapper Zukie, Iggy, Paley Bros., Elliot Randall, Dougherty - guitars, A. Paley - Drums, Eric Rosenfeld (Manhattan Ocean Club), March 9, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0147)
      Sides A: The Kids are Alright, You Really Got Me, No Jesterin', Parachute Woman X, The Pill X, Some Kinda Wonderful, Route 66*, Getting Married, Ain't it Strange ()
      Side B: Gimmie Some Lovin' [], 96 tears [], Use to Love Her, Can't Explain @ ^
      Container Annotation: X D. Johansen, () Tapper Zukie, [] Iggy, ^ Paley Bros, * Elliot Randall, @ Dougherty -g- vocal, A. Paley- drums, Eric Rosenfeld
    - Patti Smith Group - Live CBGBs, NYC 2 Jun '77 Basic Training III, June 2, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0148)
      Side A (44:31) Hunter, Magellan, Under My Skin, Jailhouse Rock, Kimberly, Redendo Beach, Space Monkey, You Really Got Me, Jolene, Ask the Angels
      Side B (32:36) Time is on My Side, Radio Ethiopia, R'n'R Nigger, Pumpin', -encores-, Piss Factory, Gloria
      Container Annotation: Performance and all material copyright by Patti Smith Group/ 1977. All commercial rights retained. Cr0z Digital Stereo
    - Patti, Palladium, May 20, 1978 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0149)
      Side A: RnR Nigger, Set Me Free, Victory, Kimberly, Space Monkey, Kids Are Alright, 26 Floor, [Track Unknown], Time is on My Side
      Side B: We Three, [Track Unknown]
    - Patti Smith Live March 22nd at CBGBs, Bleecker & Bowery, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0150)
      Side A: Piss Factory, Don't Take My Harp Away (From Me), (Patti Smith and Tom Verlaine), Green Money, Break it Up
      Side B: Land
      Patti Smith- vocals, Lenny Kaye- guitar. Prop. of P. Dougherty 212 544 9224
    - III Patti 76/77 Village Gate poetry, 1976/1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0151)
      Side A: Fear of the BOC Reaper, Birdland, My Generation (Daniel J.), Sympathy for the Devil
      Side B: Marquee Moon[redaction], Will Hollywood Ever Learn, Neo Boy, Fire of Unknown Origin, Precious Little, Babble Field
    - New Year's Eve 76/77. Cale/ Patti Smith Group? [written over], December 31, 1976 - January 1, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0152)
      Side A: Leaving it Up to You, Gun --> Pablo Picasso, Heartbreak Hotel, Waiting For My Man, Land of 1000 Dances, Ask the Angels, Redondo Beach, Free Money
      Side B: Dig, Space Monkey, Pissin' in the River, Pumpin', Ain't it Strange, 1977, (Dark Star), Land
    - P.S. [Patti Smith] Group, March 10th 77, March 10, 1977 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0153)
      Gimme Some Lovin, The Kid, You Really Got Me, No [Jesterity]
    - Patti Smith, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0154)
    - Lou Reed - live at the Geneva Theatre 10/30/76, October 30, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0155)
      Sides A: Sweet Jane, Good Time Music, Lisa Says, Kicks, She's My Best Friend, Waiting For My Man, Sheltered Life, They're Taking The Children Away, [Track Unknown], Vicious Circle, Coney Island Baby, RocknRoll Heart
      Side B: Charlie's Girl, Kill Your Sons, Satellite of Love, How Do You Think It Feels?, Temporary Thing, (encores-->) RocknRoll, Heroin, Sister Ray
    - John Cale/Church & Anthrax, Vintage Violence. Recorded in Dolby 12/29/76, December 29, 1976 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0156)
      Content
      Side A (Church & Anthrax): Church of Anthrax, The Hall of Mirrors in the Palace at Versailles, The Soul of Patrick Lee, Ides of March, The Protégé. Terry Riley, John Cale, Adam Miller
      Side B (Vintage Violence): Hello There, Gideon's Bible, Adelaine, Big White Cloud, Cleo, Please, Charlemagne, Bring It On Up, Amsterdam, Ghost Story, Fairweather Friend
      Container Annotation: Singles- Feel Good, Roxette, Keep It Out of Sight. Eddie & the Hot Rods- Wooly Bully, Horse Play.
    - John Cale- Paris 1919/ Academy in Peril (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0157)
      Side A: PARIS 1919: Child's Christmas in Wales, Hanky Panky, Nohow, The Endless Plain of Fortune, Andalucia, Macbeth, Paris 1919, Graham Greene, Half Past France, Antarctica Starts Here. ACADEMY IN PERIL: The Philosopher, Brahms
      Side B: Legs Larry at Television Centre, The Academy in Peril, Intro: Days of Steam, 3 Orchestral Pieces: Faust, The Balance, Capt Morgan's Lament, King Harry, John Milton-- Sylvia Said.
      Container Annotation: Richie Hayward- drums, Lowell George- guitar, Ron Wood - Track 2, The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra - 6 & 8
    - Lou Reed Live at LOEWS Syracuse NY May 7 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0158)
      Content: 1- Sweet Jane, I Wanna Be Black, For The Coach, Glory of Love, Waiting for the Man, You Can Dance, How Do You Think It Feels?, Uptown Dirt. 2- Walk on the Wild Side, What's Your Style?, Complete Tthis Story Now, White Light
    - Dils Hurrah, June 18, 1979 - June 19, 1979 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0159)
      Side A (June 18, 1979)
      Side B (June 19, 1979)
    - Velvets 6/26/70 Max's Rehearsal. Lou Reed '70, June 26, 1970 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0160)
      Sides A and B: What Goes On?, Cool it Down, New Age, Walk it Talk it, Who Loves the Sun?, I'm so Free, Can't Stand it, Walk it Talk it, Ridin to the Sun, I'm Stickin to You, Lisa Says, Kill Your Sons, Lonely Sat Nite
    - Lou - Royal Festival Hall with Spiders/Shady Grove Maryland/Lou & Tots Imperial College London, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0161)
      Side A: White Light*, Waiting 4 My Man*, Sweet Jane*, Rock & Roll (), Sister Ray ()
      Side B: White Light, Lonesome Cowboy, Pale Blue Eyes
      Container Annotation: * Royal Festival Hall w/ Spiders, () Shady Grove Maryland June 1973, 21 Oct 72 Lou & Tots Imperial College
    - Lou Reed, Live Dec 26, 1972 Ultrasonic Studios, December 26, 1972 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0162)
      Side A: White Light- White Heat, Vicious, Waiting for My Man, Walk It- TalkIt, Sweet Jane, Heroin
      Side B: Heroin (cont'd), Satellite of Love, Walk On The Wild Side, I'm So Free, Berlin, Rock 'n' Roll
    - Lou & the Tots 10/21/72 Imperial College, October 21, 1972 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0163)
      Side A: White Light, Lonesome Cowboy Bill, Waiting [For] the Man, Pale Blue Eyes, I'll Be Your Mirror, Candy Says, Sweet Jane, Heroin
      Side B: Berlin, Who Loves the Sun, I Can’t Stand It, Wild Child, Rock N Roll, Head Held High, Sister Ray, Miles End Sundown, Walk On The Wild Side
    - Velvet Underground Demos 65/66, 1965/1966 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0164)
      Side A: Ostrich, Sneaky Pete, Sheltered Life, It's Alright, The Way You Live, I'm Not Sorry, Here She Comes Now, Inside of Your Heart, Caroline Says, One of These Days, Ocean
      Side B: Rock 'n' Roll, She's My Best Friend, Sticking to You, Foggy Notion, Ferryboat Bill, Andy's Chest, Drive Me Insane, Cycle Annie, Sister Ray
    - Lou Reed Live in Syracuse May 7 1975 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0165)
      Content: Side A: 1. Sweet Jane, 2. I Wanna Be Black, 3. Football For the Coach, 4. Glory of Love (Coney Island Baby), 5. Waiting For My Man, 6. You Can Dance, 7. How Do You Think It Feels?, 8. Uptown Dirt, 9. Walk on the Wild Side. Side b: 10. What's Your Style? (Kicks), 11. Complete This Story Now, 12. White Light/ White Heat, 13. Rock and Roll. Sister Ray (cont'd). Lou Reed- vocal, guitar! Doug Yule- guitar, b. vocal. -sax. -bass. -drums. Loew's Theatre
    - Cale/ Roxy singles/ Patti Smith - Horses, undated (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0166)